Please subscribe to our channel!
Number one.
What is your name?
My name is Kaname Yoshizawa.
How did you come up with your name?
I was told it means "Kaname Yoshizawa, the key to success.
I don't really know what it means either.
What do people call you?
Lately I'm called Kanaki-kun by the members.
I probably get more nicknames than anyone else in the group.
You can call me whatever you want.
Where are you from? Tokyo.
What is your birthday? July 12.
What is your type on Monday? Type A.
What is your favorite part of your face?
My face is this double-edged eye.
What are your hobbies?
Fishing, World Heritage, Rubik's Cube, and many other things.
What are your special skills?
Ballet. I've been dancing ballet for a long time, so I think I'm good at ballet-type dancing.
Do anything interesting?
Do something funny?
What is your favorite food?
Taco rice.
What is your least favorite food?
I can't eat sweet-and-sour pork for a long time.
What is your favorite color?
Purple.
What are your strengths?
I have a low voice, so I can be comfortable with whoever I'm with.
What are your weaknesses?
Shyness.
What is your favorite saying?
A.
Laughter.
What is your challenge?
My larynx.
You know what?
I'm trying to have the best larynx in Japan.
Is there anything in your personality that you want to fix?
Yes, I do.
It's okay to be interested in various things.
But there are too many things that interest me.
I don't have enough time.
So I would like to develop the character of not being interested.
What made you laugh the most recently?
We were having a quiz on the names of Ghibli films.
One of the member's crafts completely misremembered how to read the name of a certain work.
He completely misremembered how to read one of the works.
That was really funny.
What's troubling you lately?
I dyed my hair the other day.
My hair was smooth to begin with.
But it's lost some of its smoothness, I guess.
Yes.
What is your daily routine?
Watching Candra.
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
Motionless order.
If you could use one superpower, what would it be?
I would like to fly.
If you won the lottery, what would you spend it on?
I would play the lottery again.
How would you use it?
Walking and playing with my dog, Luce.
What is your treasure?
The people I meet.
What is your earliest memory?
Touching a cicada shell when I was a little girl.
The cicada shell stuck in my thumb is probably my earliest memory.
Do you play air guitar?
Junjunjunjun.
Correct.
Who is the kindest person in the real sentence?
Jun Muto
Which is the strictest in reality?
Ryota Nakano
What is one unexpected aspect of the members?
One of us folds clothes with great care.
I think it's me.
I think I am a leader who doesn't look like a leader.
One secret about yourself that even the members don't know
I went to Korea the other day.
I forgot to bring souvenirs for the members.
I bought it in a hurry at the airport.
I'm sorry.
What's the one thing you can't lose to anyone?
The low voice.
Who would you like to meet?
Brad Pitt.
My Boomer.
Since the last craft project.
I watch Ghibli all the time.
How do you spend your day?
I love going to museums and just going out and going around the city.
What kind of kid were you?
I think I was a curious child.
Who is your favorite comedian?
Bananaman.
If the earth were to die tomorrow, what would you do?
I would like to play with the members of the group, the seven of us.
If you could be born again, what would you change into?
A dog.
If you were to write one kanji character to describe yourself, what would it be?
Long
Where would you like to travel?
I would like to go to Northern Europe.
I want to see the Northern Lights before I die.
Do you easily forget bad things? Scars?
I try to forget them as soon as I can.
What's your fetish?
Smell. I love people who smell good.
Here are some questions from our observers.
What is your favorite costume?
When we did the one-man show at Pacifico Yokohama.
I love the first white outfit.
The fur on the coat.
I think you can probably tell.
What is your favorite onigiri?
Rice cake and cheese
What do you value most?
I value the people I meet.
What is your favorite phrase in a cart you sing?
The harmony of the candles poofing.
What was your favorite event at the gymnastics festival?
The centipede race.
I think it's a competition where everyone moves their legs together.
If I'm in the back of the pack, I'm stronger.
I don't know.
If you were to reward yourself, what would it be?
Delicious sushi.
What is your favorite choreographed song?
Museum Zero.
I love the choreography of the chorus because it is linked to the lyrics.
What is your favorite food right now?
Samgyeopsal.
If you had 7 days off, what would you do?
I would like to go abroad to an English-speaking country.
I've always wanted to study English.
If there were 7 people in your family, what would they be?
Taka, my mom.
Jun, my father.
Jun, you're my grandpa.
I'm the father.
The rest are all brothers.
Kazu and the eldest.
Craft number two.
Let's see...
Ryota and Masaya, in that order.
Where do you want to sit in the classroom?
I definitely want to be at the back of the class, by the window.
I'll make Aigami in the current office.
Full of energy
Ummm...
We're running out of time, boo-tah-toe.
Did I say that? Did you?
I'm sorry. I'm not very good at writing love notes.
How would you compare the members to oden?
That's an interesting question.
Craft is konnyaku.
Takato is konpen.
Masaya, chikuwabu.
Jun-kun, kelp Kazuto, egg
Ryota, radish.
I'm going to make Atsuage (deep fried fish)
If you could change your face, what color would it be?
I would like to make it black. I think the color that suits me is black.
What was your favorite book?
Guri to Gura
What do you think is the most powerful thing in your life?
There are people with many different personalities, but what is this place where all the people at the very fringes of those personalities are gathered together?
It's like being in a different world. Just by looking at them
What is the most enjoyable song in the original?
Joy to the World. As the title says
Please express your favorite words with your face.
Please express with your face
the last month of the year
a group of people in tears
like this
What did you have for breakfast today?
What did I eat?
What did I have for breakfast? Oh!
I had tofu.
I love tofu. I ate a whole block of tofu.
Put on your best face.
What is the most relaxing or restful time of your day?
After work.
When I come home and say, "I'm home.
Luce.
When my dog greets me like I'm home.
I guess it's when my dog greets me like I'm home.
During rehearsals...
I...
Dried plums.
I need dried plums.
When I can't think straight during rehearsal
I eat something very sour or strong tasting
I feel refreshed.
What would you be if you weren't an actor or musician?
What would you be?
I don't know.
It's scary to think about it.
I don't know what I'd be doing.
I think I would have continued ballet.
And maybe I've been abroad.
I might have gone overseas to do volunteer work.
I've always been interested in that.
Did you have any episodes that inspired you?
What episodes inspired you?
When Jun-kun said he was going to try his hand at musical theater.
When I heard about his rehearsal, I was really inspired.
I think it's cool that Junkun is trying to make it a good production.
I think it's cool.
If you were an animal, what would you be?
I think I would be a cat.
If you could switch places for a day, who would you be?
I would like to be my sister.
She's so good at using the time of day.
She's so good at using the time in a day that I wonder if she's using a machine.
She can do everything at once.
That's amazing.
If you were to perform outside of Japan, where would it be?
I'd like to perform in Vienna.
Fashionable streets, fashionable costumes...
Who do you admire?
I guess I look up to Kazuto.
He has a lot of things that I don't have.
He also has a personality that I don't have.
Kazuto has helped me in many ways.
He has a cheerful personality.
When I play the role of a cheerful character, I think of how Kazuto is usually like.
I think about how Kazuto is usually like when I play a role with a cheerful personality, and it works out well.
He is the person I admire closest to me.
I recently saw Marvels.
It was great.
Different space, parallel worlds...
Marvel's stories are not so big that I can't keep up with them anymore.
What do you look for when choosing clothes?
I guess it's the size.
No matter how much I like the color or the pattern.
I don't buy clothes if they are not in the size I like.
What kind of bread do you buy at the bakery?
Hydrogen donuts
What appeals to you?
I know I've said it many times, but I think it's my low voice.
What are three good things that happened to you this week?
My dog let me hold him.
I saw a movie I wanted to see.
I woke up without using my alarm!
What gives you energy?
I think it's time to refresh myself.
What is your favorite material?
Dullness.
Dull.
Dull
Tell us about a song that you like to play.
Candles...hmm?
But I think Joker is also like me.
The strangeness that doesn't come out in front.
No one would say I'm strange, but...
It's a little bit weird.
I mean, the atmosphere is a bit weird.
And also in terms of the genre of dance
I wonder if it fits me.
Past life?
I'm curious to know what you observers thought it was.
I'm really curious.
Earthenware?
Like a common earthenware vessel.
What would you like for the last supper of your life?
I'd like to eat samgyeopsal.
Which seat on the bullet train do you prefer?
Seat A.
Seat A is usually window seat 3.
If I can't get a seat there when I go on an excursion...
I get a little frustrated every time I take the bullet train.
When I get seat B...
It's so frustrating!
I don't know which way to lean my head.
I don't know which way to lean my head, and I'm sorry if I hit my elbow when I'm playing with my phone...
I hate seat B
I hate seat B.
Where would you most like to go now?
I'd like to go to New York.
What is the most recent foreign word you learned?
Kenchanayo.
I think it means "Don't worry" in Korean.
What is the life of Zayu?
Hard work pays off.
Show us the photos you recently took of Opiniori.
The picture I took was a really good one.
This is one of my favorites.
When do you feel happy in winter?
When I wake up in the morning and get out of the covers.
I feel cold, so I go back to bed.
The moment when I put the quilt on after going back to sleep.
What four-letter idiom comes to mind?
Twelve, Twelve, Fifteen
What is your favorite photo?
What sport are you good at?
Soccer.
What is the most impressive dream you had while sleeping?
I had this dream yesterday.
I was probably thinking about today's shoot before I went to bed.
I went to see Junkun's make-up room because he was doing his make-up.
And then I went to see the make-up room... and got an oil massage.
Jun Muto was getting an oil massage.
It was very interesting.
What was your dream when you were little?
I played soccer all my life, so I wanted to be a soccer player.
I also wanted to be a bait maker when I got into fishing.
I saw an old book I found at my grandpa's house.
I saw an old book I found at my grandpa's house, and it was about a veterinarian, so I wanted to be a veterinarian.
I also wanted to be a fighter pilot after watching Top Gun.
Coffee drinker? Tea?
Coffee.
What's your favorite doughnut?
Twist.
What is your favorite dish?
Carrot slices.
I don't cook at all.
What is the most challenging thing you want to do?
Cooking.
I also want to be able to handle fish.
It would be cool if I could handle fish I caught.
It would be cool if I could even cook.
Which local language song would you like people to listen to the most?
Snow Dance
I'm coming in the winter.
I think that song goes well with winter.
What would you like to do this year?
Cleaning.
And also
I want to get rid of squares.
I know I'm running out of time.
Yes, sir.
It's the last thing I came here to do. The last thing?
If you could see a side of me you've never seen before.
I'm sure you'll like me even more.
You can ask me anything you want.